

CATALIN BABALAU Web developer

O Chisinau, Moldova

☑ catalin.babalau@yahoo.com

% 0786 00 299

SOCIAL

in @catalin-babalau

f @catalin-babalau

@ acatalin-babalau

nonitel

<> CodeWars

EDUCATION

Web Development - Front End

Zero to Mastery Academy on Udemy

Feb 2021 - Jun 2021

Erasmus Mobility

SMK University of Applied Social Sciences, Vilnius Lithuania

Feb 2017 - Jun 2017

General Management

State University of Pitesti, Pitesti Romania

2015 - 2018

Math and Sciences track

"Moldovan-Finnish" High School, Chisinau Moldova

2013 - 2015

SKILLS

Java

JavaScript

Cucumber

• Html

TestNG

Selenium

CSS

React

SQL

C#/.NET

JIRA

Git

PROFILE

I am a young IT specialist passionate about Programming, History and Economy. I consider myself as an adaptable open minded person with a critical thinking.

I like solving problems and I always say that for every problem there is at least one solution.

EXPERIENCE

QA Automation Internship

From Jun 2021 - Sep 2021 | Allied Testing

Chisinau, Moldova

Lifeguard

From Jun 2016 - Oct 2016 | High Sierra Pools Inc.

Washington DC, USA

oGCDP crew member (Volunteering)

From Nov 2015 - May 2016 | AIESEC

Pitesti, Romania

Customer support - Client service (Volunteering)

From Dec 2013 - Jan 2014 | Anrome SRL

Chisinau, Moldova

PROJECTS

Calculator CSS background generator

CSS HTML JavaScript CSS HTML JavaScript

Source code Source code See Live See Live

To do list

CSS HTML JavaScript CSS HTML JavaScript

Source code Source code See Live See Live

Free Souls Custom

CSS HTML Bootstrap MailChimp

Source code See Live

Robo Corporation

CSS HTML REACT

Timer

Source code See Live

LANGUAGES

- Romanian (native)
 - Russian (B2 C1)
- English (B2 C1)
- Spanish (A2)

INTERESTS

X S. Music Travel Cycling <> **Books** Code Photography